<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="athor_name">dr/Zakir Naik</string>
    <string name="description_author">Zakir Naik was born in Mumbai, India, in 1965. He is President
        of the Islamic Research Foundation and Chairman of the IRF Educational Trust in Mumbai. He
        graduated from the University of Mumbai, where he obtained degrees in medicine and surgery.
        He is interested in Islam and comparative religion, medicine, and social and economic welfare
        campaigns. He is an internationally renowned da‘iyah (caller to Allah, God the Creator) and
        has travelled to Canada, the United States, Australia, New Zealand, Malaysia, Singapore,
        several gulf states, and other countries around the world. He has written several books on
        Islam, science, and comparative religion, and is in the process of authoring many other
        books for non-Muslims who are interested in Islam.</string>

<string name="exist">Do you want to exit the app?</string>
    <string name="exis">Exit</string>



    <!-- menu items-->
    <string name="lang">Language</string>
    <string name="share">share</string>
    <string name="like">App evaluation</string>
    <string name="facebook">faceBook</string>
    <string name="youtube">youtube</string>
    <string name="Author">about Author </string>
    <string name="send">Send Suggestion </string>
    <!-- language-->
    <string name="lang_1">English</string>
    <string name="lang_2">русский</string><!--اللغة الروسية -->
    <string name="lang_3">भारतीय</string><!--اللغة الهندية -->
    <string name="lang_4">Deutsch</string><!--اللغة الألمانية -->
    <string name="lang_5">français</string><!--اللغة الفرنسية -->
    <string name="lang_6">Nederlands</string><!--اللغة الهولندية -->
    <string name="lang_7">Հայերեն</string><!--اللغة الأرميني -->
    <string name="lang_8">Українська</string><!--اللغة الأكرونية -->
    <string name="lang_9"> Română</string><!--اللغة الرومنية -->
    <string name="lang_10">Gjuha shqipe</string><!--اللغة الألبانية -->
    <string name="lang_11"> norsk språk</string><!--اللغة النرويجية -->
    <string name="lang_12"> magyar</string><!--اللغة الهنغارية -->
    <string name="lang_13"> Ελληνικά</string><!--اللغة اليونانية -->
    <!-- -->
    <string name="app_name">Common Questions about Islam</string>
    <string name="title0">INTRODUCTION</string>
    <string name="title1">POLYGAMY</string>
    <string name="title2">POLYANDRY</string>
    <string name="title3">HIJAB FOR WOMEN</string>
    <string name="title4">WAS ISLAM SPREAD BY THE SWORD</string>
    <string name="title5">MUSLIMS ARE FUNDAMENTALISTS AND TERRORISTS</string>
    <string name="title6">EATING NON-VEGETARIAN FOOD</string>
    <string name="title7">ISLAMIC METHOD OF SLAUGHTERING ANIMALS APPEARS RUTHLESS</string>
    <string name="title8">NON-VEGETARIAN FOOD MAKES MUSLIMS VIOLENT</string>
    <string name="title9">MUSLIMS WORSHIP THE KAABA</string>
    <string name="title10">NON-MUSLIMS NOT ALLOWED IN MAKKAH</string>
    <string name="title11">PORK FORBIDDEN</string>
    <string name="title12">PROHIBITION OF ALCOHOL</string>
    <string name="title13">EQUALITY OF WITNESSES</string>
    <string name="title14">INHERITANCE</string>
    <string name="title15">IS THE QUR\'AN GOD\'S WORD?</string>
    <string name="title16">HEREAFTER - LIFE AFTER DEATH</string>
    <string name="title17">WHY ARE MUSLIMS DIVIDED INTO SECTS/DIFFERENT SCHOOLS OF THOUGHT?</string>
    <string name="title18">ALL RELIGIONS TEACH PEOPLE TO BE RIGHTEOUS, THEN WHY FOLLOW ONLY ISLAM?</string>
    <string name="title19">VAST DIFFERENCE BETWEEN ISLAM AND THE ACTUAL PRACTICE OF MUSLIMS</string>
    <string name="title20">NON-MUSLIMS REFERRED AS KAFIRS</string>
    <!--      ////////////////////questions////////////////////////                   -->
    <string name="question0"> </string>
    <string name="question1">Why is a man allowed to have more than one wife in Islam? i.e. why is polygamy allowed in Islam?</string>
    <string name="question2">If a man is allowed to have more than one wife, then why does Islam prohibit a woman from having more than one husband?</string>
    <string name="question3">Why does Islam degrade women by keeping them behind the veil?</string>
    <string name="question4">How can Islam be called the religion of peace when it was spread by the sword?</string>
    <string name="question5">Why are most of the Muslims fundamentalists and terrorists?</string>
    <string name="question6">Killing an animal is a ruthless act. Why then do Muslims consume nonvegetarian food?</string>
    <string name="question7">Why do Muslims slaughter the animal in a ruthless manner by torturing it and slowly and painfully killing it?</string>
    <string name="question8">Science tell us that whatever one eats, it has an effect on one\'s behaviour. Why then, does Islam allow Muslims to eat non-vegetarian food, since eating of animals could make a person violent and ferocious?</string>
    <string name="question9">When Islam is against idol worship why do the Muslims worship, and bow down to the Kaaba in their prayer?</string>
    <string name="question10">Why are non-Muslims not allowed in the Holy cities of Makkah and Madinah?</string>
    <string name="question11">Why is the eating of pork forbidden in Islam?</string>
    <string name="question12">Why is the consumption of alcohol prohibited in Islam?</string>
    <string name="question13">Why are two witnesses who are women, equivalent to only one witness who is a man ?</string>
    <string name="question14">Under Islamic law, why is a woman\'s share of the inherited wealth only half that of a man?</string>
    <string name="question15">How can you prove that the Qur\'an is the word of God?</string>
    <string name="question16">How can you prove the existence of hereafter, i.e. life after death?</string>
    <string name="question17">When all the Muslim follow one and the same Qur\'an then why are there so many sects and different schools of thoughts among Muslims?</string>
    <string name="question18">All religions basically teach followers to do good deeds. Why should a person only follow Islam? Can he not follow any of the religions?</string>
    <string name="question19">If Islam is the best religion, why are many of the Muslims dishonest, unreliable, an involved in activities such as cheating, bribing, dealing in drugs, etc.?</string>
    <string name="question20">Why do Muslims abuse non-Muslims by calling them Kafirs?</string>
</resources>
